rocbattle.com 2017-12-01

# Privacy Statment

**Today's Special!!!! All beats $9.99 - Add Beats to Your Cart And** \- [Check Out Here!!!](http://rocbattle.com/add_to_cart.php)

Privacy Statement

**Your privacy is important to us.**  
This page discloses the privacy policy of True Executives, and www.Rocbattle.com. We are concerned about your privacy and the security of your important personal information. We want you to be aware of what kind of information we obtain from you, how we use this information, and how you can control its use. By using this site, you consent to this Privacy Policy. Rocbattle.com operates under the name of True Executives. True Executives is the parent company of these companies, and as such, when you provide information to any of these entities, this information may be combined or shared between current or future True Executives entities and subsidiaries.

**What personally identifiable information is collected?**  
In order to provide you superior service, communicate marketing promotions which we believe will be of interest to you, and to administer our business, Rocbattle.com may gather the following personal information (except where prohibited by law): salutation, name (first/middle/last), company name (if applicable), email address, phone/fax number (if applicable), payment type (VISA, Check, Cash, etc.), credit card type/number/expiration date. How this information is used and how we protect information collected from online purchases is explained below.

**How is the collected information used?**  
True Executives and Rocbattle.com uses your personally identifiable information to provide superior service in the following areas: respond to your customer service inquiries or requests, hold contests, giveaways, drawings and promotions; administer shopping or reward club accounts; conduct and administer surveys; mail marketing/sales material via email or postal mail; set up commercial accounts; sign up for new credit card promotions; or use it for other general business purposes to further enhance our business relationship with you. To enhance your Rocbattle.com experience, we may also collect aggregate information as to which pages you visit, search terms used, etc. - in order to measure the effectiveness of our website and identify areas for improvement (site performance and/or to streamline the purchasing processes).

**How do we use cookies and technology in our website?**  
Our web server collects the addresses of the web sites that visitors came from before visiting our site, which browser was used to view our site and search terms entered on our site. Without making use of any personally identifiable information, we may track the pages visited to help us understand how customers use our site. This helps us make decisions on how to create a better experience for you in the future.

**Who are the third party entities with whom we may share your personally identifiable information?**  
**Third party service providers:**  
True Executives uses third party companies in limited ways.

We may provide your information to reputable organizations that help us to fulfill services to you on our behalf. For example, we use may use companies to authorize credit card transactions, and to administer service programs, etc. We may provide information to others to help us maintain records and analyze sales data. We use customer information providers to augment and improve the accuracy of our customer database. We hire third parties to distribute postal and email communications with our offers or important information on our behalf.

The third party companies we hire are not authorized to use your information for any reason other than to provide the above stated services for which we contract them to perform.

**How do we handle information related to children?**  
This site is not intended or designed to attract children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly or intentionally obtain any personally identifiable information from any person we know to be under the age of 13.

**How can you contact us with questions regarding this Privacy Policy?**  
If you have questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, you may contact us by writing to: inquiries@Rocbattle.com. Please remember to include your postal address, email address and phone number with your correspondence.

**How am I notified of Privacy Policy changes?**  
As we continue to grow our businesses and improve our services, we reserve the right to change or modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If there are changes or additions, we will post those changes here or in other formats we deem acceptable, so that you are aware of such changes. If this Privacy Policy changes in such a way that your personally identifiable information may be used or shared in a different manner, you will be given the opportunity to opt-out of having your information used or shared in that new manner. If you are concerned about how your information is used, please check back at this site periodically.

**Disclosure exceptions:**  
Notwithstanding the above policies, we reserve the right to disclose your personal information to appropriate third parties if we are required to do so by law or we believe that such action is necessary: to comply with legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order; to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our website. To protect True Executives rights and property; or during emergencies, such as when we believe some ones physical safety is at risk. In addition, as we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer information, email addresses, and visitor information are generally among the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or any dissolution, including, but not limited to, a bankruptcy proceeding. The effective date of this Privacy Policy is April 1, 2006. It was last updated on April 1, 2006.
